Finding Aid for the National Hispanic Media Coalition Subject Files PASC.0278
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Latinos Issues Forum - news bulletin, (1998 Feb) (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Laura Salinas - resume and master's thesis: Latinas in Broadcast Journalism, University of TX, Austin (1995), (ca. 1996) (Box 7, Folder 9)
- LAUSD (Los Angeles Unified School District) agenda - Affirmative Action Advisory Committee on Employment, (1991 Jan 9) (Box 30, Folder 4)
- LBA (Latin Business Association) - newsletter, (1987 Oct) (Box 23, Folder 2)
- LCOM (Latino Committee on the Media) -Chicago Region - conference schedule, media directory and TV guide (in Spanish), (ca. 1986-1987) (Box 22, Folder 17)
  No statistical information included.
- Lee Baca - letter to Alex Nogales requesting endorsement for office, (1997 Nov 10) (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Letters - Latino community concerns and support, (1995-1998) (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Letters of commendation to media from NHMC, (1987) (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Letters of Solicitation (CORP) - NHMC's requests for financial support, (1987 June, Aug) (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Letters of Solicitation (ORGS) - NHMC's requests for financial support, (1987 July) (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Letters out - outreach to La Opinion, (1995 Oct 19) (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Liberman, [Leonard] - complaint against KKHJ, (1998-1999) (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Liberty Hill Foundation - grant information, (1997 June) (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Los Angeles County Human Relations Commission - Media Image Coalition - retreat materials, (1995 June) (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Los Angeles County Public Library - literacy referral directory, (1987-1988) (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Los Angeles TV Stations - Hispanic employee hiring statistics, (1996) (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Los Angeles TV Stations - rankings according to percentage of Hispanic employees, (1995-1996) (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Lou Correa - LA Times clipping, (1996 Dec 6) (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Lucille Roybal - complaint generated from Bob Thompson, (1994 May 20) (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Lucy Hernandez - samples of sponsorship events, (1995 Aug 16) (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Luis Miranda - New York State Puerto Rican/Hispanic Task Force banquet - invitation, (1996 March 11) (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Luis Pelayo - Hispanic Council - Chicago area concerns, (ca. 1996-1997) (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Luis Rossi - Rossi Enterprises overview, (1996 Dec 20) (Box 10, Folder 2)
- LULAC (League of United Latin American Citizens) - correspondence and organization concerns, (1993-1997) (Box 13, Folder 3)
- LULAC (League of United Latin American Citizens) -roster of Board of Directors, (1995) (Box 4, Folder 11)
- LULAC (League of United Latin American Citizens) Texas - state convention kit, (1995) (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Lupe Ramos - St. Jude Children's Research Hospital fact sheet, (1996 July 2) (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Luz Leguizamo - resume, (1996 Aug) (Box 7, Folder 16)
- MAC Affirmation Action Symposium (Minorities and Communication Division) - program materials, (1996 March) (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Macario Ramirez - Carlos Aguilar's termination at KTRK TV, (ca. 1995) (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Manny Mendoza - letter to Taco bell regarding ABC, (1995 March) (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Manuel Pastor, Jr. - Latinos and the Los Angeles Uprising: The Economic Context summary report, (no date) (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Manuel Sanchez - HispanStar clipping and resume, (1998) (Box 13, Folder 6)
- MAPA (Mexican American Political Association) - complaint against ACSA (Administrator of CA School Association), (1996-1997) (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Margaret Tobey - KCAL-TV license renewal-FCC decision, (1996 June 6) (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Margarita [Cannon] - letter about Hispanic Film Project production costs, (1997 July 30) (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Maria D'Amezcua - resignation, (1996 July 19) (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Maria Elena Durazo - New Otani Hotel boycott, (ca. 1995-1996) (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Maria Elena Gaitan - Chola con 'Cello booking information, (1996 March 7) (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Maria Roblero - resume, (no date) (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Maria Verdugo - timesheets, (1997) (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Mariachi/Calexico - thank you letter to Alex Nogales, (1997 March 27) (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Marina Montenegro - letter to NHMC seeking financial sponsorship, (no date) (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Marise Samiter - script feedback for La Sirena de Barro, (1998 March 4) (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Market Segments, Inc. - company information, (no date) (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Marketing Hispanics - clipping, (no date) (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Marlon Brando - thank you letter from NHMC, (1996 May 1) (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Marta Garcia - ABC boycott press release draft, (1995 April 20) (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Marta Montoya - Los Kitos company information, (1997) (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Marta Montoya - Los Kitos project, (ca. 1996) (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Martin Luther King Hospital - New Times LA clipping, (1997 Dec) (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Martin Quiroz - letter of complaint from NHMC, (1993 Aug 12) (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Martinez, Michael N. - endorsement letters, (1989 Oct) (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Mary Duron - Sumitomo Bank financial pledge to NHMC, (1997 Sept 22) (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Mary Helen Barro - resume, (1993 Aug 24) (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Maureen Lesoud - LA Times clipping, (1997 Jan 14) (Box 13, Folder 13)
- MCA Universal - letter to Cheryl Leader - optical prints, (1992 April 22) (Box 19, Folder 11)
- MCA/Universal general information - LA Times newspaper clipping, (1987 Aug 27) (Box 22, Folder 10)
- MCA/Universal Executive Recruitment - resumes, (1987 Aug-Sept) (Box 22, Folder 9)
- MECHA (Movimiento Estudiantil Chicano de Aztlan) - national conference information, (1997) (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Media Advisory - FCC petition against Howard Stern press release, (1995 Sept) (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Media Summit '95 - planning and information materials, (ca. 1995) (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Media Summit 97 - planning materials, (1997) (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Memo for all broadcast clients - FCC rules - station operations and filing procedures, (1998 Oct 26) (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Mercedes Ramos - complaint letter about job promotion practices, (1997) (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Mexican American Opportunity Foundation - organization information, (ca. 1994-1996) (Box 7, Folder 17)
- MGM - LA Times clipping, (1997 Feb 12) (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Mi Familia - La Opinion clipping and statistics, (1995 May-June) (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Miami [NHMC] Chapter - complaint against WPLG-TV Latino employment, (1998 Oct 22) (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Miami region - NHMC outreach letters to Hispanic community organizations, (1987 Aug, Oct) (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Michael Eisner - clippings, (1997) (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Michael R. Capizzi's - response to Committee on House Oversight interrogation, (1997 Oct) (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Michael Ruiz - letter to Alex Nogales, (1997 April 27) (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Migdia Varela - discrimination claim vs Writers Guild of America, (ca. 1995-1997) (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Mike Pyles - NBC job description, (1996 Dec 12) (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Mike Ramirez - TTMA (Texas Talent Musicians Association) complaint against Howard Stern, (1995-1997) (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Mike Tafoya - complaint against WPRR (FM), (1993 March 17) (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Miller Brewing Co - letters about sponsoring NHMC newsletter, (1989) (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Miluka Rivera - complaint - Screen Actors Guild, (ca. 1995-1996) (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Minorities and Women in Television: Adjusting the Image - Los Angeles County Commission on Human Relations conference materials, (1988) (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Minority Commercial Broadcast Ownership - report published by the National Telecommunications and Information Administration, (1996 April) (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Minority Media and Telecommunications Council - memo to Gannett Broadcasting for job fairs, (1998 Dec) (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Minority Media and Telecommunications Council - monthly reports and information on activities, (1994-1995) (Box 24, Folder 7)
  With FCC's tax certificate policy. Possibly Armando Duron's file.
- Minority Pensions - LA Times clipping, (1996 Nov 21) (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Minutes - Board [of Directors] Meeting - agenda and minutes, (1994-1997) (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Minutes - NHMC meetings, (1999 Jan-March) (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Mona Rivera - resignation letter to NBC4, (1996 May 1) (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Monarch Litho Inc. - Save These Dates stationary proofs, (1999) (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Mucho Morales - termination from KRLA, (1996) (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Music Industry - LA Times clipping, (1995 Dec 8) (Box 4, Folder 15)
- NAACP - statement of Fair Share Principles, (no date) (Box 26, Folder 3)
- NABET (National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians) - ephemera and clippings protesting ABC/Disney, (1997) (Box 14, Folder 1)
- NAHJ (National Association of Hispanic Journalists) - 15th annual convention materials, (1997) (Box 14, Folder 2)
- NAHJ (National Association of Hispanic Journalists) - newsletter, (1987 Aug) (Box 23, Folder 8)
- NAHN (National Association of Hispanic Nurses) - newsletter, (1997 Aug) (Box 14, Folder 3)
- NAHP (National Association of Hispanic Publications) - National Convention materials including press release and program, (1988) (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Nanoia, [Frank] - HAMAS (National Hispanic Academy of Media Arts and Sciences) fundraiser proposal, (1988 Oct) (Box 21, Folder 22)
- National Association of Broadcasters - Daily Variety clipping, (1994 June 16) (Box 21, Folder 18)
- National Black Media Coalition - 14th annual media conference materials, (1987 Oct 2) (Box 23, Folder 12)
- National Black Media Coalition - informational pamphlet and newsletter, (1988) (Box 37, Folder 9)
- National Council of La Raza - ALMA/BRAVO Award - ephemera, (ca. 1994-1997) (Box 8, Folder 17)
  With Center for Media and Public Affairs report "Distorted Reality: Hispanic Characters in TV Entertainment" by S. Robert Lichtner and Daniel R. Amundson. 1994 Sept 1.
- National federation of Hispanics in Communications - Washington region informational materials, (1987) (Box 22, Folder 18)
- National Hispanic Bar Association - request for NHMC organization information, (1987 Sept-Oct) (Box 23, Folder 4)
- National Hispanic Congressional Caucus - NHMC's request to present media strategy (draft), (1997 Jan 6) (Box 14, Folder 4)
- National Hispanic Leadership Agenda - follow-up letter to Federico Pena, Dept. of Energy Secretary, (1997 Dec 31) (Box 14, Folder 5)
- National Hispanic Media Dallas - proposal to Frank Newton (NAHJ) from NHMC for panels presentations at National Hispanic Media Conference, (1987 Nov 7) (Box 23, Folder 15)
- National Politics - LA Times clipping, (1995 Sept) (Box 4, Folder 17)
- National Puerto Rican Forum - conference promotional material, (1989 Oct 25) (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Native American - Mohican mascot clippings, (1997 Aug) (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Nativo Lopez - NHMC letter campaign against Enriquetta Ramos, (1996-1997) (Box 14, Folder 7)
- NATPE (National Association of Television Program Executives) - program materials, (1995-1997) (Box 31, Folder 11)
- NBC - NHMC's FCC petition to deny license renewal, (ca. 1996) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  With letter to William Caton about Young Broadcasting of Los Angeles.
- NBC Job Postings, (1996) (Box 9, Folder 12)
- NCLR (National Council of La Raza) - report titled: Distorted Reality: Hispanic Characters in TV Entertainment, (1994-1995) (Box 21, Folder 19)
  With NCLR (National Council of La Raza) 1995 Annual conference program.
- Negative publicity and Puerto Ricans - clippings, (1997 June-July, Sept) (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Neighbor Helping Neighbor Group - complaint against councilman Mike Hernandez, (1997 Sept-Oct) (Box 14, Folder 9)
- New Jersey Public Broadcasting - annual employment report, (1988) (Box 27, Folder 9)
- News Watch - Unity '94 project report, (1994) (Box 21, Folder 20)
- NHMC - Alex Nogalesfaxed communication to board members, (1997 Aug) (Box 14, Folder 14)
- NHMC - appears to be file of items to be sorted and filed, (ca. 1994-1997) (Box 14, Folder 16)
  NHMC board meeting minutes, community correspondence, CA Advisory Committee testimony, among other records.
- NHMC - board meeting agenda, meeting announcements, (1994) (Box 25, Folder 1)
- NHMC - Certificates of incorporation, (1988, 1991) (Box 25, Folder 2)
- NHMC - invoices, payment notices, expenses, and financial report, (1987) (Box 22, Folder 34)
- NHMC - list for petitions to deny license renewals, (1988-1996) (Box 18, Folder 18)
- NHMC - Long range plan fiscal years 1988-89 through 1993-94 - annotated draft, (1989 May 21) (Box 25, Folder 3)
- NHMC - Media clippings, (1986-1987) (Box 22, Folder 37)
- NHMC - meeting agendas, (1988-1998) (Box 38, Folder 1)
- NHMC - meeting notices, agendas, handwritten notes, etc., (1987, 1990, 1993) (Box 27, Folder 10)
- NHMC - National network contacts hand written notes, (no date) (Box 22, Folder 1)
- NHMC - press release, fact sheets '87 prepared by HPRA (Hispanic Public Relations Association)/Renteria, (1987) (Box 22, Folder 39)
- NHMC - retreat agenda and handwritten notes, (1995 Feb 4) (Box 25, Folder 4)
- NHMC - Steering Committee meeting minutes, agendas, status updates, among others, (1987) (Box 22, Folder 35)
- NHMC - Steering committee/Board meeting notes, agendas, etc., (1986-1989) (Box 29, Folder 1)
  Appears to be strategic planning with some references to merger between Hispanic Media Coalition and Hispanics for Fairness in the Media.
- NHMC - Texas 1990 radio renewals, (1989 Dec 11) (Box 26, Folder 11)
- NHMC [Board of Director meeting?] Agenda[s], (1995-1997) (Box 9, Folder 9)
- NHMC 10th Anniversary Banquet - planning materials and sponsorship information, (ca. 1996) (Box 8, Folder 22)
- NHMC 10th Anniversary Banquet and Impact awards - planning materials and invoices, (ca. 1996) (Box 8, Folder 20)
- NHMC 501 filing - letter from Barbosa and Vera, (1989 Dec 11) (Box 26, Folder 5)
- NHMC '96 Banquet - 10th Anniversary - script, (ca. 1996) (Box 8, Folder 21)
- NHMC Account - bank balances, (1996 Dec 12) (Box 9, Folder 8)
- NHMC Ads - ABC/Disney and clippings, (1997) (Box 14, Folder 17)
- NHMC blank membership forms, (no date) (Box 22, Folder 2)
- NHMC Board Meetings, (1995-1998) (Box 4, Folder 22)
  With agendas and supplemental information from 1996, 1997, 1998. May not be complete documentation for those years.
- NHMC Board meetings - minutes, agendas, etc., (1990-1997) (Box 9, Folder 10)
- NHMC Board of Directors Retreat 95/96 - agenda, minutes, and planning materials, (ca. 1996) (Box 8, Folder 23)
  With snapshots from NHMC banquet - 1996.
- NHMC By-Laws, (no date) (Box 26, Folder 7)
  Three copies included maybe different versions.
- NHMC Chapter chairs information regarding retreat, (1999 April-May) (Box 16, Folder 27)
  Includes agenda, NHMC by-laws, clippings, among others.
- NHMC concerns re: Telemundo - notes, clippings, research, communications, (1987-1990) (Box 29, Folder 7)
- NHMC Executive director - job description, (no date) (Box 22, Folder 30)
- NHMC Financial Report - end of Dec 31, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- NHMC flyer - Howard Stern demonstration, (July (no year)) (Box 14, Folder 18)
- NHMC fundraising letter - samples, (1996 April 25, 1995 Nov 30) (Box 6, Folder 11)
- NHMC -general information, (1988) (Box 38, Folder 9)
- NHMC grant application responses from Rockefeller and Ford Foundations, (1990 Jan) (Box 37, Folder 4)
- NHMC graphics, (no date) (Box 22, Folder 32)
- NHMC Houston - LULAC (League of United Latin American Citizens) District XVIII convention keynote speaker invitation to Alex Nogales, (1997 Feb 12) (Box 13, Folder 22)
- NHMC interoffice memos, (1987) (Box 21, Folder 23)
- NHMC KMEX - ratings information, (1987) (Box 22, Folder 12)
- NHMC Latin File NPR - audiocassette, (1989 June) (Box 26, Folder 20)
- NHMC meeting of 10-17-95 - announcement, (1995 Oct) (Box 4, Folder 20)
- NHMC New York - meeting announcement, (1996) (Box 9, Folder 13)
- NHMC New York region - NHMC outreach letters to Hispanic community organizations, (1987) (Box 22, Folder 22)
- NHMC notes of daily tasks, to do list, meeting notes, (1997-1998) (Box 15, Folder 21)
  Appears to be notes for staff member.
- NHMC Petitions to Deny - station list, (1988-1996) (Box 12, Folder 10)
- NHMC Positive Images newsletter, (1996 Fall) (Box 15, Folder 22)
- NHMC Positive Images newsletter - annotated, (1987 Fall) (Box 22, Folder 25)
- NHMC Positive Images Spring edition newsletters, (1988-1989) (Box 26, Folder 9)
- NHMC Retreat (2-23-95) - agenda and clippings, (ca. 1995) (Box 4, Folder 19)
- NHMC sample letter of support for Hispanic employment (at KCBS), (1987 April 16) (Box 22, Folder 3)
- NHMC San Diego - reception and news conference materials, (1997 Feb) (Box 14, Folder 19)
- NHMC Seminar - Cultural Issues and the Latino Population materials including various job postings, (1996) (Box 9, Folder 11)
- NHMC Sponsors - financial pledges, (1997 July-Aug) (Box 14, Folder 11)
- NHMC State [Compensation Insurance] Fund - policy change, (1997 June 16) (Box 14, Folder 12)
- NHMC Steering Committee - agendas, notes, communications, etc., (1991) (Box 29, Folder 6)
- NHMC Steering Committee agenda and list of East Coast Hispanic Media advocates, (1989) (Box 26, Folder 10)
- NHMC takes action against California radio stations - press release, (1990 Oct 30) (Box 26, Folder 6)
- NHMC Universal/MCA - Hispanic employment and representation, (ca. 1986-1987) (Box 22, Folder 8)
  With letters, chronologues and other information generated by HAMAS.
- NHMC website - email communication from German Aranda to Alex Nogales, (1997 Nov 12) (Box 14, Folder 15)
- NHMC Weekly Bulletin, (1995 July) (Box 5, Folder 20)
- NHMC, New York - information requests and newsletter draft, (1998-1999) (Box 18, Folder 5)
- NHMC, Phoenix Chapter - orientation announcement, (1999 Jan) (Box 18, Folder 6)
- NHMCgram - blank stationary, (no date) (Box 26, Folder 8)
- NHMC's National Board of Directors -Directory, (no date) (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Nielsen Ratings - clippings, (ca. 1995) (Box 4, Folder 18)
- NLCA (National Latino Children's Agenda) - organization information, (1995 Aug-Sept) (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Nolan A. Bowie - Racial discrimination in the motion picture and television industry: solutions for survival - draft of speech delivered to SAG and AFTRA, (1986 March 9) (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Norma Cobb - correspondence from Alex Nogalesabout NHMC, (1996 June 5) (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Norma Silva - miscellaneous communication to Alex Nogales, (1997 Aug, Oct) (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Nosotros - Golden Eagle Awards program, (1996) (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Nosotros - Nosotros 18th anniversary program and El Diario clipping about Raul Yniguez, (1988) (Box 26, Folder 12)
- NOW (National Organization for Women) - Fight the Right March ephemera, (1996 Feb) (Box 8, Folder 18)
- October 1990 newsletter - form letter for financial support, (1990 Oct 26) (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Offers - invitations to speak at or attend events, (ca. 1995) (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Olivia Glauber - NHMC financial data, (1995-19970) (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Opera singer - LA Times Magazine clipping, (1999 March 7) (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Orange County community forum - complaints about Robert Dornan, (1997) (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Orange County mental health - LA Times clipping, (1997 Aug 10) (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Oscar Sendowsky - IRS penalties - NHMC, (1995 Nov 30) (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Parade - NHMC entry form for LA Mexico's Independence parade, (1987 Sept 13) (Box 22, Folder 41)
- PBS (Public Broadcasting System) - position vacancies, (1989) (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Pedro Infante Foundation - press release, (1996 April 8) (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Pepe Barreto - 1995 Billboard Award nominees, (1995 July) (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Pepe Motta - resume and CD, (no date) (Box 4, Folder 26)
  With Marta Motta resume.
- Pepe Vargas - Chicago area concerns, (ca. 1995) (Box 4, Folder 27)
  With Chicago Latino Film Festival programs from 1996-1997.
- Pepper and Corazzini - legal services and expenses, (1992 Aug) (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Pepper and Corazzini - letters from Bob Thompson to various people, (1989-1990) (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Pepper and Corazzini communication, (1994 March - April) (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Perenchio FCC Application for acquisition of Univision, (ca. 1992) (Box 32, Folder 6)
  FCC form 315.
- Personas Mayores Manual de Ayuda - Spanish resource pamphlet for Orange County distributed by KABC and Home Savings, (1988) (Box 25, Folder 23)
  Distributed by KABC and Home Savings.
- Petition to Revoke [licenses] - list of radio stations, (no date) (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Petitions to deny license renewals - filed by NHMC, (1997 Oct) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  Stations: KAVL, KKHJ (AM),KLON, KLSX (FM), KBZT, KIFM, KVCR, KHJJ, KGMX.
- Phil Roman - Latin Heat clipping, (1997 July/Aug) (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Phillip A. Martinez - business letter to Alex Nogales, (1997 Feb 12) (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Photographs - [NHMC first major fundraiser Aug 1987?] - 30 items, (ca. 1987) (Box 22, Folder 36)
  Includes the following: 21 - color prints, 5 - 5x7's, and 4 - 8x10's.
- Picket Phone lists, (1995 May) (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Pilar Montoya - Jeff Katz complaint, (1996 Aug) (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Pledges - support of action against ABC-TV, (ca. 1995) (Box 4, Folder 21)
- PMAA (Personnel Management Association of Aztlan) - filings against WFBR, KGO, and KRON license renewals, (1988) (Box 26, Folder 15)
- PMAA (Personnel Management Association of Aztlan) - licensed renewal challenge, (1988-1989) (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Portada - press kit featuring Teresa Rodriguez, (1988) (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Power 96 FM (KPOW) - request to withdraw petition to deny license renewal filed by NHMC and SALAD (Spanish American League Against Discrimination), (1989 Dec) (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Power of Attorney and PSJ declaration of representative, (1990-1991) (Box 20, Folder 13)
- President Cliton [Clinton] - copy of inaugural address and LA Times clipping, (1996-1997) (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Press conference 11/3/97 - action against Disney/ABC press release, (1997 Nov) (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Press conference 4/24/97 - Disney/ABC boycott planning notes, (1997 April) (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Press Conference 9-26-95 - fax coversheets about KLSX and Howard Stern, (1995 Sept 26) (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Press Release fax covers, (no date) (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Press Releases, (ca. 1995) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  ABC boycott, Howard Stern, NBC Latino employment, among others.
- Press releases - NHMC's action against ABC/Disney, (1997) (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Prime Time '95 - fall schedule, (1995 May 25) (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Professional Unions - list, (1996-1997) (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Project Info [Community Services] - 25th anniversary invitation to Alex Nogales, (1997) (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Proposition 187 - clippings, (ca. 1995) (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Proposition 187 aftermath - clippings, (ca. 1994-1995) (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Proposition 187 fundraisers - MALDEF (Mexican American Legal Defense and Educational Fund) - 187 information, (1994 June-July) (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Proposition 209 [affirmative action legislation] - clippings, (1996-1997) (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Propositions - LA Times clipping, (1996 Dec 22) (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Puerto Rican and Hispanic American discrimination - hearing transcripts, (1993 Oct 18) (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Purchase Orders - Marlon Brando interview from Larry King Show, (1996 April 11) (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Radio ratings - clippings, (1995-1998) (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Radio stations [So. CA] - listing from unidentified publication, (ca. 1997 Oct 2) (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Radio Unica - clipping, (no date) (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Radio/Porno - La Opinion and LA Times clippings, (1997 Jan-Feb) (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Radio/Television Public Inspection check list, (1995 April) (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Rainbow Coalition - collaboration with NHMC, (1994-1996) (Box 31, Folder 17)